NGUYỄN BÁ HƯNG

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

Contact

HCM, Vietnam

+84 869 052 629

<u>bahung1221.github.io</u>

bahung1221@gmail.com

bahung1221

in linkedin.com/in/bahung1221

Skills

FE - HTML, CSS, JS, VueJS, Tailwind

••••

BE - NodeJS

••••

BE - PHP

DE C.I.

BE - Golang

Databases - MySQL, MongoDB

• • • • •

DevOps - Unix/Linux, Server Management

....

DevOps - Git, SSH, Docker, GoCD

••••

Mobile - Flutter

••••

Soft skill - Task management, Collaboration,

Problem Solving

UX - UX Design, User-oriented thinking

• • • • •

Languages

English (reading, writing, listening)

English (speaking)

• • • • •

About Me

5 years of experience in the software industry, with nearly 4 years in the Fullstack Developer role (Frontend Heavy).

Currently working on an outsourcing startup, so I have the chance to work on all aspects of production-grade products.

I am also a member of <u>Grokking VN</u>, which is an organization passionate developers can share fundamental knowledge with each other.

My pros are research and self-learning skills since new things always pique my curiosity.

My target is to become a Software Architect in the near future.

Education

Bachelor in University of Science, VNUHCM

09/2015 - 09/2018

Information Technology

Work Experience

SaigonTek 12/2019 - Present

Fullstack Developer / Solution Architect

- Developed 4+ products for VN & JP customers, mostly for the JP market.
- Worked on all aspects of the development processes: Requirement analytics, Planning, Wireframe review, Task Management, Development, and Monitoring.
- Contributed to some OSS projects on Github: <u>shopify/draggable</u>, <u>conwnet/github1s</u>, and so on.
- Tech Stack: VueJS (Nuxt), Tailwindcss, NodeJS, PHP, MySQL, Linux cloud servers, AWS (EC2, ALB, S3, VPC, Route53, SES, and so on), GoCD, Flutter.

Gogojungle VN 12/2017 - 12/2019

Junior Fullstack Developer

- Developed & maintained an e-commerce system for the Japanese market.
- Worked on all three Frontend, Backend & DevOps teams
- **Tech Stack**: VueJS, PHP (Laravel), NodeJS, MySQL, Linux cloud servers.

Certificates

UX Design Fundamental - Nordic

06/2021 - 08/2021

 Learned the standard UX design process. It helps me empathize with designers and product owners.
Thereby creating a better product for the end-users.